▍2026 美网 女单半决赛
萨巴伦卡 7-5 6-2 佩古拉 · 赛后场上采访
Aryna, that was a flawless performance
阿丽娜 今晚这场太完美了
by you tonight No complaints,
挑不出一点毛病
I'm just super happy that I was able
我特别开心 自己能
to pull out such tennis Last match I played
打出这样的球 上一次
against Jessica.
我对上杰西卡
It was almost impossible for me
那场球我几乎
to get the win.
赢不下来
So I'm super happy that I was able
所以我真的很开心
to Play such tennis in front of you all.
能在你们面前打出这样的球
Thank you for thank you
谢谢你们 谢谢
for the atmosphere
谢谢这样的气氛
and honestly guys you You're the best
说真的 各位 你们太棒了
your respect to me is priceless
你们给我的尊重 千金不换
and I really appreciate that you I know
我真的很感激 我知道
that you wanted her to win It's obvious,
你们本来希望她赢 这很明显
but thank you for being so respectful to me.
但还是谢谢你们这样尊重我
Thank you. Love you guys What
谢谢 爱你们
felt different about this match
这场球和上一场有什么不同
and how were you able to play
你是怎么做到
so well for the entirety of it?
整场都保持这个水准的
I don't know. I was so desperate
我不知道 我太想赢了
to win. I wanted it badly
就是特别想 特别特别想
and I was just trying to focus on myself
我只是努力专注在自己身上
and then guys look
还有 各位 你们看
at my box. I couldn't fail in front
看看我的包厢 我不能输
of all of those Legends beautiful girls
在那些传奇 那些漂亮姑娘面前
the best people and my team of course.
最好的人 当然还有我的团队
I love you guys Well,
我爱你们
you're into your fourth straight US
你连续第四次闯进美网决赛
Open final you've done this a few times
这件事你已经做过好几回了
Do you have any rituals that you'd like
你有什么固定的仪式吗
to do before the final here in New York
在纽约打决赛之前
or are you gonna keep it the same?
还是一切照旧
Oh, yeah, I do.
有 当然有
I have my favorite breakfast
我有我最爱的那顿早餐
I have my dinner the dinner
还有那顿晚餐
that has to be done even like last
那顿是雷打不动的 就像昨晚
night Polo Bar they had private event,
Polo Bar 本来有私人包场
but Just because I have my ritual.
但就因为我有我的仪式
They really squeezed me in
他们硬是给我挤出了位置
and I felt like I really broke
我都觉得自己是闯进了
into someone else's night,
别人的场子
but thank you. Thank you for Polo Bar.
但真的谢谢 谢谢 Polo Bar
Thank you Nelly for squeezing us in
谢谢他们给我挤出时间
My routine really means a lot to me.
我这套流程对我真的很重要
And yeah, I definitely got some
所以是的 我一定照办
We'll allow you to start your routine now.
那现在就让你去走你的流程
done tonight looking forward to seeing you
今晚打得漂亮 决赛见
in the final ladies and gentlemen.
女士们先生们
Well, number one Aryna Sabalenka back
世界第一 萨巴伦卡
in the US Open final
重返美网决赛